Guide to the Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management records,1993-2012.
Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management records,1993-2012
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management records, 1993-2012.
23-26-3006
New York State College of Human Ecology. Dept. of Policy Analysis and Management.
4 videotapes and 5.6 cubic ft.
Reports, minutes, course materials, videotapes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Course material, reports, committee meeting minutes, plans and proposals concerning the Department of Policy Analysis and Management and material relating to the merger of the Department of Human Service Studies and Consumer Economics and Housing.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1998, the Department of Consumer Economics and Housing and the Department of Human Service Studies merged to become the Department of Policy Analysis and Management.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Course material, reports, committee meeting minutes, plans and proposals concerning the Department of Policy Analysis and Management and material relating to the merger of the Department of Human Service Studies and Consumer Economics and Housing. Includes videotapes with Policy Analysis and Management faculty appearances: Jennifer Tiffany, "Talking with Kids About AIDS"; Andrea Parrot on Larry King Live; Roger Battistella on health care reform.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; Battistella, Roger M.; Parrot, Andrea.; Tiffany, Jennifer.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Human Ecology. Dept. of Human Service Studies.; New York State College of Human Ecology. Dept. of Consumer Economics and Housing.
Subjects:
AIDS (Disease)--Study and teaching.; Medical care.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.library.cornell.edu/handle/1813/531
SERIES LIST
Series I. Reports, Plans and Proposals
Series II. Course Material
Series III. Merger Related Material
Series IV. Faculty Material: Meeting Minutes, Memos, Grants
Series V. Committees
Series VI. Correspondence
Series VII. Budgets and Funding
Series VIII. Publications and Publicity
Series IX. Photographs
Series X. Events
Series XI. Videos
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Reports, Plans and Proposals
  - Diaz Proposal - partnership between Cornell and Florida International University, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Folders 2 and 3 formerly contained Faculty Annual Reports - these contents are now in Box 7 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Department Review - Consumer Economics and Housing and Human Service Studies correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Self Study and Plan (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CLASP-transfer of CLASP from Policy Analysis and Management to the Department of Education-correspondence, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Department Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Department Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Department Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Strategic Plan-draft, 2000-03-01 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Plan and External Review material- draft, 2001-02 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Plan, 2001-03 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - External Review, 2001-11 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - External Review Report, 2002-01-28 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - External Review Report, 2002-05-02 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Response to Recommendations of the 2002 Review of Policy Analysis and Management, 2004-05 (Box 3, Folder 24A)
  - Department Profile, 1999-09-27 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Academic Plan for the creation of Policy Analysis and Management, 1996-07 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Proposal - Justification and Proposed Model for a Graduate Program in PAM; Proposal from State Education Department to change M.S. and PhD degree titles from Human Service Studies to Policy Analysis and Management, 2000, 1999-09 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Policies on Space, Administrative Structure, Teaching Assistants and Phones, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Policies on Smith-Lever, Voting, Travel, and Income, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Consolidation Committee Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Policies and Procedures Manual, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Academic Program Review Information, 1999-06 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Proposal for a Visiting Fellows Program, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "An Investigation into the Feasibility of Raising the School-Leaving Age in New York State"-Rosemary Avery, Laura Colosi, Jerome Ziegler, 2005-06 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - The Long Island Opening Adoption's Door to Teen Project Final Evaluation Report - evaluation conducted by Rosemary Avery, 2010-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Annual Reports
    See additional faculty reports in electronic format in collection #23-2-2817
    - Allen, Josephine, 1977-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Avery, Rosemary, 1988-2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Barr, Don, 1983-1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Battistella, Roger, 1984-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Battistella, Roger, 1991-2003; 2206 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bristow, Barbara, 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bryant, W. Keith, 1975-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Burkhauser, Richard V., 1998-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Butler, J.S., 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Calori, Cynthia, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Cawley, John, 2001-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Chi, Peter, 1976-2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Colosi, Laura, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Delara, Thom, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Dimmler, Laura, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dunifon, Rachel, 2001-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dyer, Margaret, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Ford, John L., 1976-1992 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gans, Jon, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Geddes, Raymond Richard, 2002-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Gerner, Jennifer, 1974-1982; 1984-1995; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Greene, Jennifer, 1984-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Hahn, Alan, 1966-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Heath-Crump, Ossie, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Heck, Ramona, 1978-1993 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Heck, Ramona, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Hollis, Brooke, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Joyner, Kara, 2000-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Kabcenell, Andrea, 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Kenkel, Donald, 1995-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Kuder, John M., 1992-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Kutty, Nandinee, 1995; 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, Jeffrey, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Lillard, Dean R., 1991-2008 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lucarelli, Claudio, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Mathios, Alan, 1992-2003 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - McClintock, Charles, 1976-2000 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Miles, Sue, 1984-1998 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Morton, Lois, 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mueller, Jeanne, 1977-1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Nicholson, Sean, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - O'Neill, Liam, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Parrot, Andrea, 1983-1994 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Parrot, Andrea, 1994-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Peters, H. Elizabeth, 1994-2002; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Pollak, Patricia, 1984-1993 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Pollak, Patricia, 1993-2003 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Reeves, Terrie, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Rendall, Michael, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Rodriguez, Eunice, 1993-2002 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Rosen, William, 1991-2003 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Roufaiel, Nazik, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Sassler, Sharon, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Schultz, Jennifer, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Simon, Kosali, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Swanson, Josephine, 1981-1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Swanson, Josephine, 1991-2003, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Swisher, Raymond R., 2001-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Tennyson, Sharon, 1998-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Tiffany, Jennifer, 1991-2003 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Tobias, Donald J., 1984-2003 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Trochim, William, 1983-2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Unur, Ali Sinan, 2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Waldron, M. Kristine, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Waller, Maureen, 2003-2006 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Walston, Stephen, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Wang, Hua, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - White, William D., 2003; 2006 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Series II. Course Material
  - Human Service Studies (HSS) Courses - Spring, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Spring, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Spring, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Spring, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Spring, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Fall, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - HSS Course Syllabi - Spring, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - HSS Course Syllabi, 1988-93 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Consumer Economics and Housing (CEH) Course Syllabi - Spring, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Spring, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Fall, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Spring, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Fall, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Fall, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Spring, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Fall, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Spring, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Fall, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - CEH Course Syllabi - Spring, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Policy Analysis and Management (PAM) Course Syllabi - Fall, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - PAM Course Syllabi- Fall, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Spring, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Fall, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - PAM 220-"Introduction tom Management Principles and Differences Among Sectors", 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Spring
  - Economics - Concentrations, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Management Curriculum, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - PAM Course Syllabi, Spring 2006 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - PAM Course Syllabi, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Fall
  - PAM Course Syllabi, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - PAM Course Syllabi, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - PAM Course Syllabi, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - PAM Course Syllabi - Emily Owens, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Series III. Merger Related Material
  - Merger - courses (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Merger related articles (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Course material for Introductory Macroeconomics, 1996-97 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Draft plans for the merger of HSS and CEH (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Merger documentation, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Merger documentation, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Merger Committee - Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Merger Committee - Administration, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Merger Curriculum Committee, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Merger-Extension Committee, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Merger-recruiting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Merger-Steering Committee, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Merger-Steering Committee, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Steering Committee-courses at Cornell that could support an Academic Plan for a merged dept. -family, consumer, health basics, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Careers after Cornell-PAM, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Video-Welfare Policy Debate (Box 1)
  - Formation of PAM-Academic plans, correspondence, revision and adjustment, faculty meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Research-some newspaper clippings, 1995-03-1996-01 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee meeting minutes, correspondence, 1996-01-1996-03 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Solidification plans, minutes, 1996-04-1996-06 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Solidification plans, minutes, 1996-04-1996-06 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Merger Committee - Graduate School Organization, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Series IV. Faculty Material: Meeting Minutes, Memos, Grants
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1997-08-1998-10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1998-11-1999-03-02 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1999-03-17-1999-08 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1999-09-1999-12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2000-01-2000-08 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2000-09-2000-12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2001-01-2001-05 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2001-09-2001-04 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2002-05-2002-08 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2002-09-2002-12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-01-2003-02 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-03-2003-06 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-09-2003-12 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-09-2003-12 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2005-08-2005-12 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Department Memos to Faculty, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Department Memos to Faculty, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Department Memos to Faculty, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Department Memos to Faculty, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Grants, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Citations of the Work of Tenure Track Faculty in PAM, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Mentoring and Voting" Procedures for Tenure, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Position Descriptions, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Advising Handbook, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Series V. Committees
  - Executive Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Educational Policy Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Policy Seminar Committee, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Series VI. Correspondence
  - Burkhauser, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Burkhauser - reviews of various papers, 2000-01-2001-04 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Burkhauser - reviews of various papers, 2001-04-2001-08 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Burkhauser - reviews of various papers, 2001-12-2002-03 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sloan Directorship, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sloan Program, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Money 2000" - Statewide Financial Education Program, includes Fitness Workbook, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sr. Extension Associate Position - Jeanne Hogarth, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cooperative Extension, 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Space issues in the Department, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Public Policy - Cornell Institute for Public Affairs, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Public Policy - Cornell Institute for Public Affairs, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Students - grant information, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mentoring/Tenure, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Tenure Reviews-memos, 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ethics and Pubic Life Program, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Social Work Program Vote, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Experiential Learning, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Anonymous Donors - Undergraduate Teaching Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Series VII. Budgets and Funding
  - Budget Narrative-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Budget Narrative-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Budget Narrative-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Budget Narrative-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Budget Narrative-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Budget Narrative-Policy Analysis and Management, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Budget Narrative-Policy Analysis and Management, 1999-05 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Budget Narrative-Policy Analysis and Management, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hatch Act Allocations, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Budget/ Planning Conference-items for discussion with Dean, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Series VIII. Publications and Publicity
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 1984-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2008-2010 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Publicity-articles and reports about the department, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Faculty publications, 2010, 2011; CD 1841-1842 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Faculty publications, 2012, 2013; CD 1843, 2032 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Faculty publications, 2014; DVD 1229 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Faculty publications, 2015; DVD 1513 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Faculty publications, 2016; DVD 2669 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Policies and Procedures Handbook, 1998-01 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Policies and Procedures Handbook, 2000-01 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Policies and Procedures Handbook, 2000-09 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Graduate Handbook - Human Service Studies, 1998-08 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Handbook-Consumer Economics and Housing, 1998-08 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Best of Policy Analysis and Management Website Handbook, 1998-12 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Series IX. Photographs
  - Photographs-Department Parties, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs-Department Parties and Retreat, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs-Department Parties and Offices, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs-Staff Summer Retreat, 2001, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photographs-Staff Retreat and Staff, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Series X. Events
  - Lecture at Duke Theology and Medicine Program-Jerome Ziegler, 2006-11 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - McCain vs. Obama in 3D: Data and Debate on Domestic Policy, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Series XI. Videos
  - "Talking with Kids About Aids" with Jennifer Tiffany, V-416 (Box 8)
  - Andrea Parrot on Larry King Live, 1993; V-417 (Box 8)
  - "Health Care Reform: The Public Pulse" WKSGTV, 1993; V-418 (Box 8)
  - Roger Battistella-WSKGTV, 1993; V-419 (Box 8)